Stanislaw M. Ulam Papers 1916-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.54
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional correspondence, 1932-1986, 15.5 Linear feet 33 boxes
  - Harris, Theodore E., 1946-1950 (Box Series I-12)
  - Harrison, Marvin [S.?], 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hartgering, James B., 1962 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hartzman, Carl S., 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Harvard University Society of Fellows, 1957-1975 (Box Series I-12)
    Hoxie, E. F.
    Leontif, Wassily
  - Hatch, Eastman N., 1974 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hay, Patricia, 1942 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hawkins, David (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #1, [1945?]-1973 (Box Series I-12)
      Primes, MANIAC
      See Peters, Max
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
      Ulam, Claire
    - Folder #4, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
      Stats., philos.
  - Hawkins, Thomas, 1983 (Box Series I-12)
  - Haworth, Leland, 1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heady, Ferrel, 1969 (Box Series I-12)
    Hon. degree
  - Heatherly, Henry E., 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heisenberg, W., 1965 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hejtmanek, Hans, 1969-1982 (Box Series I-12)
  - Helfenstein, H., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heller, Robert L., 1978 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heller, Sidney, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hellerman, Leo, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hellerman, Robert H. G., 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Helson, Henry, 1951-1958 (Box Series I-12)
    See Steinhaus, Hugo
  - Hempelmann, L. H., 1945 (Box Series I-12)
    LASL health hazards
  - Hendrickson, M. S., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henkin, Leon, 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henney, Dagmar, 1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henniart, Guy (Box Series I-12)
    See Duclaud-Lacoste, Pascal
  - Henningsen, Peter, 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hénon, Michel, 1967 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henri, [?], 1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henrick, John J., 1960 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henriques, F. C., 1956 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hensley, Douglas, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Herbstein, F. H., 1977-1978 (Box Series I-12)
  - Herman, Bob (Robert), 1969-1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Herman, Gabor T., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hermann, Robert, 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hermes, Henry, 1972-1976 (Box Series I-12)
    SIAM
  - Herz, J. C. (Jean-Claude), 1965; 1967 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hessel, Samuel J., 1979 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hestenes, M. R., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heuer, Ken, 1975; 1980 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hewitt, Edwin, 1947; 1960-1961 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hewlett, Richard G., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Higier, Theodore, 1964 (Box Series I-12)
  - Higman, Howard, 1964 (Box Series I-12)
    Conf. on world affairs
  - Hill, Albert G., 1962-1964 (Box Series I-12)
    Wiesner, Jerome B.
  - Hilton, Peter, 1967 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hines, Richard P., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hirschfelder, Joseph O., 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoarse, Graham, 1980-1981 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hobbs, Arthur M., 1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hodges, Andrew P., 1979 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hodges, John H., 1970-1973 (Box Series I-13)
    Griffin, Edmond E.
  - Hoerlin, Hermann, 1956; 1961 (Box Series I-13)
    LASL space committee
  - Hoffman, Frederick, 1974 (Box Series I-13)
    talk outlines
  - Hofstadter, Douglas R., 1977-1981 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hofstadter, Robert, 1975 (Box Series I-13)
    See also Fieser, Louis F.
  - Holladay, John C., 1964-[1977?] (Box Series I-13)
  - Hollis, William H., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-13)
  - Holsztynski, Wlodzimierz, 1975-1979 (Box Series I-13)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1977 (Box Series I-13)
    re: Adventures
    Klein, Norman
  - Holter, Norman J., 1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - Holton, Mary, 1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Honig, William, 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hooper, Jane, 1954 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hopf, H., 1936; 1951 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hopkins, Frank S., 1940 (Box Series I-13)
  - Horowitz, A., 1956-1957 (Box Series I-13)
    chess
  - Horwitz, Paul, 1969 (Box Series I-13)
    ABM issue
  - Householder, A. S. (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #1, 1948-1956 (Box Series I-13)
      Monte Carlo, Mathematical Profiles Project (MPP)
    - Folder #2, Nov. 1956 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #3, Dec. 1956 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #4, 1957 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #5, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Howard, William M., n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Howorka, Edward (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #1, 1973-1978 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #2, 1979-1981 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
      SMU's notes
  - Hoyt, Henry, 1949; 1958; 1969 (Box Series I-13)
    LASL security of top secret docs.
  - Huang, Kerson, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hudson, Craig C., 1960 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hughes, A. L., 1943-1944 (Box Series I-13)
    Invitation to Los Alamos
  - Hunter, Kenneth E., 1963-1970 (Box Series I-13)
    Hycon
  - Hurd, Cuthbert, 1949-1983 (Box Series I-13)
    Monte Carlo
  - Hyers, Donald H. (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #1, 1942-1954 (Box Series I-13)
      USC; papers
    - Folder #2, 1955-1982 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #4, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
  - Hyman, [A?nton] A., 1961 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ickes, Harold, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    ABM
  - Ihrig, Edwin (Box Series I-14)
    - Folder #1, 1980-1981 (Box Series I-14)
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Ilisevich, Robert D., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Inghram, Mark G., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ingraham, R[ichard L.], 1952-1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
    Scott, Cynthia
    Vilkas, Eduardas
  - Interscience Publishers, Inc., 1957-1960 (Box Series I-14)
    Collection of Mathematical Problems
    Kask, Warren
    Kent, Leonard B.
    King, Charles H.
    Mosbacher, C. J.
    Proskauer, E. S.
  - Irwin, John, 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Irwin, William J., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Isa[?]dor, Wladimir, 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Isaacs, Rufus, 1957-1958 (Box Series I-14)
    Game theory
  - Iseki, Kiyosi, 1939 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ivry, Benjamin, 1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jacob, George, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jacobs, Earl E., 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jacobsen, Thomas W., 1982 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jaffe, Robert L., 1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Janssen, William Earl, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jarmie, Nelson, 1958 (Box Series I-14)
    LASL
    Bradbury, N. E.
    Froman, D. K.
  - Jaworowski, Jan, 1958; 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jehle, Herbert, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jensen, Hans D., 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jessor, Richard, 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Joffe, Anatole, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - John, Fritz, 1952-1961; 1971 (Box Series I-14)
    problems
  - Johnson, Donnelly J., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Gordon G., 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Laurence W., 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Paul B., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Ralph M., 1972; 1976-1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Ralph P., 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - Johnson, Shirley, 1972; 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, Burton W., 1957-1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, James P., 1983 (Box Series I-14)
  - Jones, R. Michael, 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Just, Kurt, 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - K[?], E[?]l, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kac, Mark (Box Series I-14)
    - Folder #1, 1955-1964 (Box Series I-14)
      See Preece, Warren E.
    - Folder #2, 1965-1968 (Box Series I-14)
      Mathematics and Logic; Rota comments
      Borgese, Elizabeth Mann
    - Folder #3, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-14)
      Reviews
    - Folder #4, 1971-1978 (Box Series I-14)
      Some in French, Lebesque
    - Folder #5, 1979-1983 (Box Series I-14)
      Some in Russian
    - Folder #6, n.d. (Box Series I-14)
      Marceli Stark, Adventures
  - Kadushin, Evelyn G., n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Kahane, Joseph, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kahn, Herman, 1949; 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kakutani, Shizuo, 1941; 1950-1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kalk, W. Richard, 1982 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kallet, [Tony], 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kallman, Robert R., 1973-1979 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kalman, Rudolph, 1974; 1979 (Box Series I-14)
    See also Whitman, Marina von Neumann
  - Kaluza, Roman, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
    Some in Polish, Banach
  - Kamimura, K., 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kampe de Feriet, J., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kannai, Y., 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kantor, Jean-Michel, 1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaplan, Wilfred, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaplanski, Irving, 1963; 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - Karff, Mona M., 1981 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kariotis, Christina, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Karlsson, Johan, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Karpinski, Marek, 1977-1980; n.d. (Box Series I-14)
    See Pallascke, D.
  - Karst, Edgar, 1961-1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kates, Robert W., 1977 (Box Series I-14)
    NAS-human rights
  - Katz, Paul H., 1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - Katz, Richard J., 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kauffman, Andrew J., 1957-1958 (Box Series I-14)
    Juliusz Ulam
  - Kaufman, Brian, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaufmann-Buhler, Walter, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kautz, Willam H., 1963 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaysen, Carl, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kazanowski, Albin, 1979 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keeny, Spurgeon M., 1960-1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keesling, James, 1972-1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kehl, William B., 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keilson, Julian, 1951-1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kekst, Gershon, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keldysh, M. V., 1973 (Box Series I-15)
    Sakharov
    Handler, Philip
  - Kellogg, J. M. B., 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kelly, Armand, 1949 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kelly, Harry C., 1960 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kelly, Paul (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #1, 1941-1949 (Box Series I-15)
      War years
    - Folder #2, 1955-1975 (Box Series I-15)
      Visual hull
    - Folder #3, 1976-1980 (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #4, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
      Papers
      Bondy, J. A.
      Hemminger, R. L.
    - Folder #5, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Kemeny[?], John, 1947 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kennedy, Sargent, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kepski, Julius, 1982 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kerr, Donald M., 1981-1982 (Box Series I-15)
    Metropolis, N.
  - Kershner, R[ichard] B., 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kessler, Richard Lee, 1964 (Box Series I-15)
  - Khinchin, A. I., 1951? (Box Series I-15)
  - Kiefer, J[ack], 1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kielczewski, Z., 1975 (Box Series I-15)
    Nowak, S.
  - Kiesler, Bruno, 1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - Killian, J. R., 1956 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kilmer, William L., 1962 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kim, K. J., 1981; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Kimball, R. M., 1949 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kimble, H. Jeff, 1982 (Box Series I-15)
  - King, Donald West, 1972; 1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - King, Gilbert W., 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - King, Percival, 1967 (Box Series I-15)
    Fermiac calculator
  - Kingman, John, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kishimoto, Akitaka, 1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kisiel, Chester C., 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kissell, Mary C., 1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kisslinger, Carl, 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kister, Jim, 1956-1957 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kistiakowsky, George B., 1959-1977 (Box Series I-15)
    Muskie campaign
  - Klamkin, M. S., 1959 (Box Series I-15)
    Newman, D. J.
  - Klaring, Wermer, 1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Klauder, John R., 1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kleban, Eugene, 1974; 1977 (Box Series I-15)
    Polish Institute of Arts and Sciences in America
  - Klee, Victor, 1958; 1973-1974 (Box Series I-15)
    See also McCarthy, Joseph L.
  - Kleene, Stephen C., 1940-1942; 1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - Klein, Jacob, 1956 (Box Series I-15)
  - Klein, Morris, 1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kleinberger, P. A. (Mrs.), 1963 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kleinfeld, Erwin, 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kleitman, Daniel, 1961-1976 (Box Series I-15)
    Erdö
  - Kleppner, Adam, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Klethyn, Anatol, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
    anagrams of SMU's name
  - Kletzing, Dennis, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kline, J. R., 1942-1945 (Box Series I-15)
    war
  - Kluczynski, Thomas E., 1964 (Box Series I-15)
  - Knee, David, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Knight, Bruce, 1973 (Box Series I-15)
  - Knight, Gary A., 1981 (Box Series I-15)
  - Knudsen, Vern O., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kobelinski, Mitchell P., 1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kochen, Manfred, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-15)
    Wilson, Linda M.
  - Kohler, Foy D., 1982 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kolata, Gina Bari, 1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kolman, Bernard, 1983 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kolo Lwowian, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kolodner, I. I., 1971; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Kolstead, George A., 1964 (Box Series I-15)
    See Pasta, John
  - Kölzow, D., 1979 (Box Series I-15)
  - Konopinski, Emil, 1965; 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kopec, Ada, 1976-1977; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Kopman, Gerd, 1976; 1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Koprowska, Irena, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - Koprowski, Hilary, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Korevar, Jaap, 1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kosciuszko Foundation, 1974 (Box Series I-15)
    Miskiewicz, Sophia
  - Koshland, Daniel, 1981 (Box Series I-15)
  - Koski, Walter, 1947 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kott, Lidka, 1962-1963; 1975, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
    Steinhaus' daughter
  - Kouri, Robert, 1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kout, Robert T., 1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kowalik, J. S., 1982-1983 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kraichman, R., 1958 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kramer, Ernst, 1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kramish, Arnold, 1976-1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kreweras, Germain, 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Krinsky, Susan, 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Krohn, Robert, 1957; 1969 (Box Series I-15)
    Computer history
  - Kruskal, Joseph B., 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kruskal, Martin, 1953-1958; 1972 (Box Series I-15)
    See also Zabusky, Norman
  - Krzywoblocki, M. Z. E., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - Krzyzanowski, Ludwik, 1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Krzyzewski, Tadeusz, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuehne, Mary Ellen, 1967-1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kugler, Larry, 1980; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuhn, Hans, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuhn, Harold W., 1957 (Box Series I-15)
    See Luke, John W.
  - Kuiper, Gerard P., 1953 (Box Series I-15)
    Gamow, G.
  - Kunz, Jozef, 1980 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuper, Marietta, 1957-1958 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuperberg, Wlozimierz, 1983 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kupiec, Yaakov, 1977 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuratowska, Zofia, 1983 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kuratowski, Kazimierz (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #1, 1936-1958 (Box Series I-15)
      Letters from K., usually in Polish, with Ulam's responses, usually in English.
    - Folder #2, 1960-1967 (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #3, 1968-1979; n.d. (Box Series I-15)
      Mycielski, Jan
  - Kurepa, Duro, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kursunoglu, Behram N., 1983 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kymala, Earl E., 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Kyrala, Ali, 1961; 1980-1981 (Box Series I-15)
  - Labanty, [?], n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Labouygues, Jean Michel, 1981-1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lagarias, Jeff C., 1983 (Box Series I-16)
  - LaGrange, Robert H., 1966; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
    Exam
  - Lahren, Alice, 1974 (Box Series I-16)
  - Laibow, Rima E., 1981 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lam, Stanislaw, 1958 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lamm, Richard D., 1979 (Box Series I-16)
  - Land, Edwin H., 1959 (Box Series I-16)
  - Land, Frederick, 1969 (Box Series I-16)
  - Langer, Bronislaw, 1942 (Box Series I-16)
  - Langer, Rudolph E., 1942-1958 (Box Series I-16)
    Univ. Wisconsin, war
  - Lanier, Harold H., n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Larkin, Kenneth T., 1961 (Box Series I-16)
  - [Larson], Jean, 1976-1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - LaSalle, J. P., 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lasker, Edward (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #1, 1957-1963 (Box Series I-16)
      Computers, chess
    - Folder #2, 1964-1974 (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series I-16)
    - Lasky, Melvin J., 1963 (Box Series I-16)
  - Last, Jerold A., 1971-1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Las Vergnas, M. (Box Series I-16)
    -See Ser.I, Berge, Claude
  - Laub, M., 1980 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lavatelli, Leo, 1956 (Box Series I-16)
  - Laver, Rich, 1978? (Box Series I-16)
  - Lawence, George H., 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lax, Henry, 1980 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lax, Peter D., 1955-1978; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser.I, Fulks, Watson
  - Laymen, E. R., 1968 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lazarus, Roger B., 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leahey, William J., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leary, Joanna, 1974 (Box Series I-16)
    -Seealso Ser.I, Marion, Sylvie
  - Leary, Timothy, n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - LeBaron, Robert - Press Conference, n.d. (Box Series I-16)
    AEC - Eniwetok
    Cooney, James
    Dean, Gordon
    Quesada, E. R.
    Graves, Alvin C.
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1961 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lee, C. E., 1958 (Box Series I-16)
    Lark-reactor code
  - Lee, Yuk, 1983 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leff, Harvey S., 1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lefschetz, S., 1957 (Box Series I-16)
    -Seealso Ser.I, Bellman, Richard
  - Legendre, Pierre, 1969-1971 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lehmer, D. H., 1958-1965 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leibler, R., 1957 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leith, Cecil, 1969 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lelinka, B[?]dan, 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Le Lionnais, François (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #1, 1966-1972 (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #2, 1973-1979 (Box Series I-16)
      Gardner, Martin
    - Folders #3-4, n.d. (Box Series I-16)
      Games, in French, Dictionnaire des nombres remarquables
  - LeMay, Curtis E., 1962 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lenard, Andrew, 1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lennox, Edwin, 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lenz, Jerry, 1979 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leontief, Wassily, 1967 (Box Series I-16)
    -Seealso Ser.I, Harvard University Society of Fellows
    -Seealso Ser.I, Krinsky, Susan
  - Leprince-Ringuet, [?], n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Leray, Jean, 1957-1959 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lerner Publications Company, 1968 (Box Series I-16)
    Murphy, Judith
  - Leser, Arthur, 1937 (Box Series I-16)
  - LeTourneau, Budd W., 1983 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lettvin, Jerome Y., 1967; 1970 (Box Series I-16)
  - Leuchtag, H. Richard, 1978 (Box Series I-16)
  - Levée, Richard D., 1958-1960 (Box Series I-16)
  - Levenson, Norman, 1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - LeVeque, William J., 1981 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lévi, R., 1976-1980 (Box Series I-16)
  - Levin, Simon, 1981 (Box Series I-16)
    -Seealso Ser.I, American Academy for the Advancement of Science
  - Levinger, Joe, 1955 (Box Series I-16)
  - Levinson, Norman, 1956 (Box Series I-16)
  - Levy, David N. L., 1971 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lévy, Paul, 1954 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lewin, Isaac, 1965-1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lewin, Ludwik, 1969 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lewis, Albert C., 1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lewis, Ralph, 1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Libby, W. F., 1968 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lichnerowicz, A., 1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1949 (Box Series I-16)
    AEC press release
  - Lin, C. C., 1957; 1969-1971 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser.I, American Mathematical Society
  - Lind, David A., 1979 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lind, Douglas, 1966-1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lindstrom, Andrew O., Jr., 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lipetz, Milton E., 1973 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lipkin, Leonard J., 1977 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lipman, Joseph, 1979; 1983 (Box Series I-16)
  - Lippmann, B.A., 1970 (Box Series I-16)
  - Litow, B. E., n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Little, David M., 1945 (Box Series I-16)
  - Littwin, Dianne, 1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - Livingston, Robert B., 1965; n.d. (Box Series I-16)
  - Lloyd, Stuart P., 1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Loats, James T., 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lockett, Andrew M., Jr., 1977; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
    Chapter on SMU
  - Logan, Jonathan, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Loinger, A., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lomnicki, Adam, 1965-1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lomnicki, Zbigniew Alexander (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #1, 1952-1964 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #2, 1965-1969 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #3, 1970-1984?; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - London, Julius, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Long, Richard G., 1966-1967 (Box Series I-17)
  - Longuet-Higgins, H. C., 1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lonseth, Arvid T., 1958 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lopez, Robert, 1980 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lorch, E. R., 1956; 1982 (Box Series I-17)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory, 1954 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lovberg, R., 1980 (Box Series I-17)
    Feher, G.
  - Love, Thomas R., 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lovelace, W. Randolph, 1962-1965 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lovelace, Walter B., 1956 (Box Series I-17)
    Lovell, Catherine Coit
    -SeeSer.I, Coit, Catherine
  - Low, Robert J., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lowdin, Per-Olov, 1974-[1981] (Box Series I-17)
  - Lowe, Victor, 1969-1970; 1977 (Box Series I-17)
    Alfred North Whitehead
  - Lowenthal, Abraham F., 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lubinsky, Doron Shaul, 1978 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lucas, H. L., 1960 (Box Series I-17)
  - Luckow, William K., 1957 (Box Series I-17)
  - Luehr, Charles P., 1956-1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Luke, John W., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-17)
    Kirkland, T. A.
    Kuhn, H. W.
    Mauchly, John W.
    Speiser, A. P.
  - Lundell, Albert T., 1968-1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lupanov, O. B., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Luthy, M., 1972 (Box Series I-17)
    Gropetti, H.
  - Lutwak-Mann, Cecilia, 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Lynch, J. F. (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #1, 1974-1983 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Lyndon, Roger C., 1939-1941; 1968-1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Macauley, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mac Coll, L. A., 1956 (Box Series I-17)
  - MacDougall, D. P., 1957 (Box Series I-17)
  - MacDuffee, C. C., 1944; 1952; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Macintyre, Lisbeth, 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Macintyre, Walter M. (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #1, 1961-1968 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #2, 1969-1983; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Mack, J. E., 1956 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mackay, Alan L., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - MacLane, Saunders, 1937 (Box Series I-17)
  - MacNeille, H. M., 1946-1949 (Box Series I-17)
  - Macraison, Pierre J., 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Magill, Ken, 1975-1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Magnus, Arne, 1965-1968; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Maihey, George W., 1943 (Box Series I-17)
  - M[alitz?], J[erry], 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit, 1967-1982 (Box Series I-17)
  - Manley, J. H., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-17)
  - Manning, Thurston E., 1965-1969 (Box Series I-17)
    Bailey, Daniel E.
    Ellingwood, Robert
    Roberts, Dwight V.
  - Manvel, Bennet, 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marchi, Ezio, 1967-1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marcus, [?], 1979 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marcus, Richard, 1957-1958; 1979 (Box Series I-17)
    Computer card program
  - Marczewski, Edward, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marion, Sylvie, 1974 (Box Series I-17)
    Leary
  - Mark, Hans, 1982 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mark, J. Carson, 1959; 1968-1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marki, Lanle, 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Markus, Lawrence, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marois, M[aria?], 1971-1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Maroque, Joseph, 1958 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marr, Robert B., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marshak, Robert E., 1965-1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Marshall, Clifford, 1958 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martelli, Mario, 1979-1980; 1983 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martens, Jos, 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, Alistair B., 1976; 1978 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, Donald A., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, Harold W., 1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, Lorraine, 1976-1978 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, M. H., 1956-1961 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, Pierre, 1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martin, W. T., 1955-1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Martinez, Daniel, 1979 (Box Series I-17)